jumpfly.com 2015-06-07

# JumpFly Privacy Policy | All Customer Information is Safe & Secure

JumpFly respects the privacy of its users. We sometimes collect information during your visits to understand what differentiates you from each of our millions of other users.

In order to demonstrate our commitment to your privacy, we have prepared this statement disclosing the privacy practices for the entire JumpFly site. Additional terms and conditions, if any, regarding the collection and use of your information may also be provided to you before you sign up for a particular service.

Here, you will learn what personally identifiable information of yours is collected, how and when we might use your information how we protect your information, who has access to your information, and how you can correct any inaccuracies in the information.

**What Information is Collected**  
JumpFly collects certain information from and about its users in two ways—directly from the user and from our web server logs. User-supplied information: When you submit a form we may ask you for your name, email address and some other personal information. The more accurate information you volunteer, the better we are able to customize your JumpFly experience.

**Log Information**  
When you visit an internet website, you disclose certain information about yourself, such as your internet [Protocol] (IP) address, the time of your visit and the referring location (e.g., the site or page that offered a link to a JumpFly page). JumpFly, like many other sites, records this basic information about visits to its site. You should remember that whenever you voluntarily disclose personal information online, your information can be collected and used by others. Although JumpFly tries to protect your personal information, JumpFly cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to us, and you do so at your own risk. You are also solely responsible for maintaining the secrecy of any passwords you set up and/or any account information.

**How and When Information is Used**  
We use information in different ways, depending on the type of information. User-supplied information: This information is used for purposes such as personalization and verification. Web server logs: This information helps us identify which areas of our site are of interest to our visitors. JumpFly also collects the internet [Protocol] (IP) addresses of its visitors for the purposes of system administration.

**Third Party Vendors and Cookies**  
Third party vendors, including Google, will show JumpFly ads on sites on the internet. Third party vendors, including Google, use cookies to serve ads based on your prior visits to our website. You may opt out of Google's use of cookies by visiting the [Google advertising opt-out page](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html "Google advertising opt-out page").

**How We Protect Your Information**  
The privacy and protection of your personal information is vitally important to us. JumpFly does not make personal information available to any third parties without your permission. Any user statistics that we may provide to prospective partners regarding your JumpFly usage are provided in the aggregate only and do not include any personally identifiable information about any individual user.

Unfortunately, no data transmission over the internet can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. Accordingly, despite our efforts to protect your personal information, JumpFly cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to us, or to or from our online products or services. You transmit all such information at your own risk. However, once we receive your transmission, we make our best effort to ensure its security on our systems.

**Who Has Access to the Information**  
Except as described, JumpFly will not willfully disclose any individually identifiable information about its users to any third party without first receiving that user's permission. JumpFly may disclose personal information when we believe in good faith that the law requires it or to protect the rights or property of JumpFly.

We welcome any questions or comments you have about the JumpFly site.

JumpFly, Inc.  
2541 Technology Dr #414  
Elgin, IL 60124  
Ph: 877-239-9610  
Fax: 877-379-0335
